# Talha Kerpiççi

Flutter Developer

Istanbul, Turkey

📥 Aug 1999 🎽 talha.kerpicci@gmail.com 📞 +90 531 927 4988

https://www.talhakerpicci.com/ 🚺 talhakerpicci

in talha-kerpicci

Hello. I'm currently working at Borda Technology as a Flutter Developer. I have been developing mobile applications with Flutter for the last 3 years. I am seeking new job opportunities to sharpen my Flutter knowledge and skills. I am very enthusiastic to learn novelties in other branches of programming and increase my experience in a technology developing international company.

#### **EDUCATION**

(Aug 2017 - Jun 2022) **Dogus University** 

Bachelor Degree, Computer Engineering (English)

(Aug 2013 - May 2017) Kadikoy Kavram High School

High School

**WORK EXPERIENCE** 

(Sep 2021 - Present)

(Sep 2020 - Sep 2021)

**Borda Technology** Flutter Developer

Bordatech is an Industry-leading IoT for Healthcare company that brings operational awareness & insight with actionable IoT data. I currently develop the Lighthouse mobile application to allow hospital staff to manage their assets.

Flutter | Bloc | Azure | REST Services | Git | Figma

#### One Bilgi Sistemleri Ticaret A.Ş.

Flutter Developer

One Bilgi Sistemleri provides a range of consultancy and information technology focused services to leading competitive institutions. I was responsible for developing several mobile applications with Flutter and Firebase.

Flutter | Firebase | Python Web Scraping | Git | GitHub

#### **PROJECTS**

#### Simple Library

Simple Library is a personal digital library app that helps user to keep track of their books with many other features. Built with Flutter and Firebase.

GitHub: https://github.com/talhakerpicci/simple\_library

#### Marka Elcisi

A mobile app that aims to advertise a company's social media posts in a natural way by fetching Twitter and Linkedin posts of the company and shows them within the app to the user and reward the user when they like, comment or retweet a post.

# **House of Auctions**

House of Auctions is a mobile application to provide an auction enviroment for those willing to sell their items or looking to buy products. Created with Flutter (mobile) and Python Flask (backend). Riverpod | REST | Postman | PostgreSQL | Heroku

## **Exam Result Bot**

A python script automating the process of checking my exam grades. The bot would check my grades every 5 minutes which runs on my raspberry pi and notify me with an email if a new exam result has been announced.

Requests | Beautifulsoup | Linux | OpenCv | Sqlite

## **COURSES TAKEN**

## Desktop App Development

(Mar 2017 - Jul 2017)

Face to face course from Murat Yücedağ about developing desktop applications with C#.

## **Udemy Courses**

Many courses from Udemy about various topics like desktop app development with C#, REST API development with Python (Flask), and mobile application development with Flutter. Currently learning Go to develop RESTful services

## **SKILLS**

**Flutter** Linux Python Bloc, Provider, Riverpod, Freezed, Servers, Desktop, Debian, Arch Flask, Web Scraping, Scripting, get\_it and injectable Linux, Rocky Linux Selenium, OpenCV

C# Raspberry Pi SQL

MsSql, PostgreSQL Desktop Apps, .Net Core, OOP Home Server, Docker

Go Git

Api GitHub, Azure

**INTERESTS** 

Swimming **Home Lab** Reading

Calisthenics Chess **Computer Games** 

## **LANGUAGES**

## **English**

Full professional proficiency